<quiz>    <topic name="Floods">        <question>Once the lightning has stopped, it's okay to play in flood waters.</question>        <answer value="false">This is False. Never play in flooded areas! Hidden sharp objects, fallen power lines, and pollution are serious hazards.</answer>        <question>It takes many days of rain to cause a flood.</question>        <answer value="false">This is False. Most of Florida is flat land. With heavy rains, city streets and open fields can be flooded in less than an hour.  Just six inches of fast moving water can knock you down!  Stay inside until the water goes down.</answer>        <question>Standing water that's covering the road may be deeper than you think.</question>        <answer value="true">This is True.  You can't tell how deep a puddle is by looking at it. You could jump in a puddle and be over your head. Remember: Turn Around, Don't Drown!</answer>    </topic>
    <topic name="Lightning">        <question>More people die from lightning strikes in Florida than in any other state.</question>        <answer value="true">This is True.  Florida has more lightning than any other state, and many people live here. The hazard is greater for that reason. Be smart. Make sure you use the 30/30 Rule to keep yourself safe!</answer>        <question>If you see lightning, but you can count to 30 before you hear its thunder, it is okay to be outside.</question>        <answer value="true">This is True.  This is the 30/30 Rule.  You must start counting as soon as you see the flash of lighting.  Keep counting until you hear the thunder.  If thirty seconds or more have passed, it is okay to be outside. If not, go inside and wait for thirty minutes after you hear the last thunder before you go back outside.</answer>        <question>If you see lightning and hear thunder right away, you should get under a tree to be safe.</question>        <answer value="false">This is False.  When the is lightning is close like this, you should move inside right away. No baths or swimming allowed when it's lightning!  Stay away from doors, windows, and pipes or faucets.  Stay off the phone, too.  Wait for thirty minutes after the thunder has stopped before going back outside.</answer>    </topic>
    <topic name="Tornadoes">        <question>Tornadoes only happen when it's raining.</question>        <answer value="false">This is False. Often tornadoes form around hurricanes and thunderstorms, but it might not be raining right where you are. Make sure you always keep your All-Hazards Weather Radio turned on.  Make sure you have fresh batteries as a back up, too.</answer>        <question>A tornado watch means that there is a tornado coming your way!</question>        <answer value="false">This is False. A tornado watch means there are conditions that might produce a tornado.  A tornado warning means one has been spotted in your area. You should be prepared to move to a safe room should a tornado actually form.</answer>        <question>Tornadoes can occur any time of day or night.</question>        <answer value="true">This is True. This makes tornadoes in Florida even more dangerous.  If people are asleep, they many not hear warnings on the television. An All-Hazards Weather Radio will alert you to a warning at any time of day or night.</answer>     </topic>
    <topic name="Hurricanes">        <question>When a hurricane is coming, you should tape all your windows.</question>        <answer value="false">This is False. Taping your windows does no good. You should use plywood or get storm shutters to cover your windows.</answer>        <question>You should check your disaster supply kit every June.</question>        <answer value="true">This is True. This is the beginning of hurricane season. It's a good time to check your supplies, replace batteries, and rotate your stock of food and water. Remember your kit can be used for emergencies other than hurricanes, too.  Just keep it up to date!</answer>        <question>You should start tracking a storm once it's given a name.</question>        <answer value="true">This is True. Tropical storms can cause lots of wind and rain even before they become a hurricane. The good thing is, you have time to prepare. Check your disaster supply kit. Know if you live in an evacuation area. Make sure you have a family plan to deal with storm surge, flooding, or wind.</answer>    </topic>
    <topic name="Thunderstorms">        <question>Thunderstorms always have lightning.</question>        <answer value="true">This is True. Lightning is a bolt of electricity that causes the air around it to heat up very quickly. That's what causes the thunder sound you hear.</answer>        <question>Thunderstorms move very slowly.</question>        <answer value="false">This is False. Thunderstorms may move very quickly. Watch the sky.  Listen to a radio or television station or your All Hazard Weather Radio. Take cover inside a building if a strong thunderstorm approaches you.</answer>        <question>Hail is only about the size of a penny.</question>        <answer value="false">This is False. Hail as big as a baseball or larger has happened 35 times in the last 50 years in Florida. Hailstones can damage cars, windows, and roofs of buildings. Do not go outside if it is hailing.</answer>    </topic>
</quiz>