<keywords language="english">
	<keyword>
		<word>character</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[something that makes their clubhouse different from others]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>bolted</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[ran quickly]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>scurried</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[moved quickly]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>hurricane</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[a storm with winds faster than 74 miles per hour: Hurricanes usually come with heavy rain and flooding, lightning, thunder, and often tornadoes.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>All-Hazards Weather Radio</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[These special radios are the direct link between the National Weather Service meteorologist and the public.  They broadcast weather news within seconds of release.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>tracking the storm</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[This relates to listening to the weather reports and plotting the latitude and longitude of a storm’s center on a map.  Doing so over time shows the path of the storm.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>Disaster Supply Kit</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[This is a collection of items that every Florida household should have on hand at all time in case of an emergency.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>restocked</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[filled up again, re-supplied]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>pre-packaged</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[those foods that are canned, bottled, or otherwise prepared so that they do not need to be kept cold or cooked.  This is important part of a disaster supply kit, as the electricity may be out for several days at a time in the event of a hurricane.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>bands of rain</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[Hurricanes and other tropical storms almost always  produce lines of showers and thunderstorms that can sometimes show up as strips or stripes of clouds in the sky.  Rain and sunny weather may alternate frequently as the rain bands pass over.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>eye of the storm</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[the center of a hurricane. As the eye passes overhead, the winds die down to nothing.  This can be very dangerous, as people may believe the storm is over.  But when the eye travels past, the most dangerous hurricane winds hit instantly!  On a satellite image, the eye shows up as a dark spot in the middle without clouds.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>evacuating</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[leaving an area. Evacuation routes should be researched and decided long before the time when bad weather threatens.  Evacuation should also be done far enough in advance of a storm so that you are not trapped in your car on the road.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>gusting</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[a brief rushing of lots of wind all at once.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>The National Hurricane Center</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[The National Hurricane Center/Tropical Prediction Center is co-located with the National Weather Service Miami Forecast Office on the main campus of Florida International University in Miami, Florida. Weather updates about hurricanes are generally released from this office of the National Weather Service.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
	<keyword>
		<word>storm surge</word>
		<definition>
			<![CDATA[refers to a large dome of water 50 to 100 miles long that sweeps across the coastline near where a hurricane makes landfall.  The stronger the hurricane and the shallower the offshore water is, the higher the surge will be.]]>
		</definition>
	</keyword>
</keywords>